JOHANNA RIQUELME A

D09P2N3 - Drumcondra | 0899749357 2023094@student.cct.ie - MSc in Data Analytics - CCT College, Ireland · linkedin.com/in/johannariquelme https://github.com/Johanna23cct/first-project-cv

Professional Profile:

With over 20 years of technical support experience.

My focus on customer service, technical excellence and SLA management.

I encourage continuous improvement. As a bilingual professional,

I communicate effectively in two languages, greater market reach.

I am dedicated to growth, I seek certifications to stay at the forefront.

I am ready to contribute technical expertise and collaborate to drive success.

Employment History:

Nov 2022 - Present: Seller, Cinders's Shoes, Dunnes Stores - Stephen Green

- Retail experience in customer service and expertise
- Consistently achieved top position in seller ranking

I can gladly show if necessary the figures of my accumulated sales for the year.

These numbers speak of my commitment and success in the field.

My tasks include stock control, maintaining products on display, receiving delivery from the central warehouse and organizing it in the store's internal warehouses, as well as shipping between stores, customer service and after-sales.

Sep 2022 - Nov 2022: I was living in Germany

Oct 2021 - Sep 2022: Gastronomy and Barista Staff, Excel Recruitment and Loss&Co.

- Developed career in gastronomy and customer service
- Worked with major companies such as Guinness Storehouse, Aviva Stadium.
- Obtained FETAC Level 6 Certified Trainer and barista certifications

2019 to 2021nProgram Woman Head of Household, project: Kostum2020

Position: Entrepreneurship in costume design and tailoring

- Studied Ing at UBO University, through this program

March 2018 to June 2019

Cym Southwest Gas

Position: Administrative processing of collections

Preparation of payment statements, input of documentation

into the ERP system from Spain, SAP, and Excel databases,

and billing using the SII system.

December to February 2018

MANPOWER Temporary Services

Position: Payment Control Administrator at METROGAS S.A. Income, supplier payment management using the SAP system, data extraction to Excel spreadsheets, collaborative tasks with accounting to request invoice payments, and communication with suppliers for payment issuance.

January to May 2017

Customs Agency BROWNE and Co. Ltd. For Bata Chile S.

Position: Foreign Trade Administrative

Analysis of accounts for foreign trade suppliers, responsibilities

linked to Accounting and Finance, direct communication with suppliers.

January to May 2016

Freight Forwarders CONFIA CARGO S.A.

Position: Operations & Customer-S Dept. (internship for graduation)

Creation of importation folders, support for the Operations Department.

2009 - 2015: Freelance Art Visual, Owner of Own Project in Work Art

1989 - 2008: Help Desk, Telephone Support (Level 1) and Laboratory (Level 2)

- Supported various important companies in Chile
- Managed system failures, software and hardware configuration, and reporting I have letters of reference from four of the companies where i worked in this area with which I can demonstrate my experience and functions in more detail if required.

JOHANNA RIQUELME A

2023094@student.cct.ie - MSc in Data Analytics - 0899749357 - CCT College, Ireland · linkedin.com/in/johannariquelme https://github.com/Johanna23cct/first-project-cv

Education & Qualifications:

February 2023 to June 2024: MCs Data Analytic, CCT College, Dublin Ireland March 2019: Business Engineering, University UBO, Chile (Not Graduated) March 2014 to June 2016: Business Administration, CFT Manpower, Chile March 1986 to December 1989: Programmer Technician Diploma, Institute San Luis

Interests / Extra-curricular:

I have developed volunteer service through Vineyard and volunteer to visits St John of God Hospital, in Dublin I have mastered the art of painting in oil I participated in exhibitions in Chile and Embassy of Chile in Dublin

References:

Marguireta Heger Real Estate Consultant at New England Preferred Properties Email: marguireta@marguireta.com

Ms. Sinead Dunne Excel Recruitment

Email: Sinead.dunne@excelrecruitment.com

Phone: 087 701 2094

Ms. Yeiza Yegres SOUTHWEST CyM Agency Chief of Staff

Email: yeiza.yegres@cymsoeste.com

LOOKING FOR SUMMER INTERNSHIPS & GRADUATE OPPORTUNITIES 2023/2024 Employment permit status Stamp 2: Eligible to work 20 hours in term time. and next year, Stamp 1G: Available to work full-time.

September 2023, Dublin.